sangeethamobiles.com 2017-08-04

# Sangeetha Mobiles : Pioneer then Leader Now

We provide these privacy highlights for your convenience but we encourage you to review the full Sangeetha mobiles Private Limited, Bangalore, India. Collection, Use, Disclosure, and Security of Personal Information 

We collect personal information when you use our services or otherwise interact with us, including information you provide, such as contact information, billing & credit information, and resumes; information that is automatically collected, such as details about use of our services and our Web pages  and information from other sources, such as credit reports and mailing lists. 

We use personal information for various business purposes, such as to complete transactions and bill for products and services; respond to requests for service or assistance; create and improve products and services; suggest additional or different products or service; and protect our rights and property. 

We do not sell, rent, or provide personal information to unaffiliated third-parties to market their products and services to you. We may disclose personal information to unaffiliated third-parties who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf and under certain other limited circumstances, subject to restrictions on the third-parties’ use of such information. We use a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information and we use reasonable procedures to erase or render it unreadable when we dispose of it. 

**Access and Choice**  
You may access and modify your contact information by visiting sangeethamobiles.com, visiting a Sangeetha mobile retail store, or by contacting Customer Service. If you are a Sangeetha customer and you manage your account online, you can change your marketing preferences by logging into your my Sangeetha Profile. 

**Other Privacy Information**  
We do not solicit children to purchase our services or products and our Web sites are not designed to attract children under the age of 13. We may use cookies, Web beacons, and similar technologies. Sangeetha follows the Best Practices Guidelines for Location-Based Services. 

With your consent, we may provide location-based services or provide access to location information so third-parties may provide you such services. 

When you install third-party applications on your device, you may give your consent for the third party to access certain information you have stored on your device or to access Sangeetha network information to facilitate the application’s functions. 

**Policy Updates and Contact Information**  
We may update this policy from time to time and you should refer to it often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes. If we intend to use or disclose personal information in a way that is materially different from that stated in this policy at the time it was collected, we will post notice of the change on our Web site’s home page for at least 10 days before we implement the change and give you an opportunity to opt-out of the proposed use. 

If you have questions, comments, or concerns about this policy or about Sangeetha privacy practices, you may contact us through support@sangeethamobiles.com or using the other contact information provided in the full privacy policy.
